<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <title>Jask Don</title>
  
  <subtitle>a freedom writer</subtitle>
  <link href="https://wyt.icu/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
  
  <link href="https://wyt.icu/"/>
  <updated>2024-10-07T12:06:56.627Z</updated>
  <id>https://wyt.icu/</id>
  
  <author>
    <name>Jask Don</name>
    
  </author>
  
  <generator uri="https://hexo.io/">Hexo</generator>
  
  <entry>
    <title>Hello World</title>
    <link href="https://wyt.icu/2024/10/07/hello-world/"/>
    <id>https://wyt.icu/2024/10/07/hello-world/</id>
    <published>2024-10-07T12:06:56.627Z</published>
    <updated>2024-10-07T12:06:56.627Z</updated>
    
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Welcome to <a href="https://hexo.io/">Hexo</a>! This is your very first post. Check <a href="https://hexo.io/docs/">documentation</a> for more info. If you get any problems when using Hexo, you can find the answer in <a href="https://hexo.io/docs/troubleshooting.html">troubleshooting</a> or you can ask me on <a href="https://github.com/hexojs/hexo/issues">GitHub</a>.</p><h2 id="Quick-Start"><a href="#Quick-Start" class="headerlink" title="Quick Start"></a>Quick Start</h2><h3 id="Create-a-new-post"><a href="#Create-a-new-post" class="headerlink" title="Create a new post"></a>Create a new post</h3><figure class="highlight bash"><table><tr><td class="gutter"><pre><span class="line">1</span><br></pre></td><td class="code"><pre><span class="line">$ hexo new <span class="string">&quot;My New Post&quot;</span></span><br></pre></td></tr></table></figure><p>More info: <a href="https://hexo.io/docs/writing.html">Writing</a></p><h3 id="Run-server"><a href="#Run-server" class="headerlink" title="Run server"></a>Run server</h3><figure class="highlight bash"><table><tr><td class="gutter"><pre><span class="line">1</span><br></pre></td><td class="code"><pre><span class="line">$ hexo server</span><br></pre></td></tr></table></figure><p>More info: <a href="https://hexo.io/docs/server.html">Server</a></p><h3 id="Generate-static-files"><a href="#Generate-static-files" class="headerlink" title="Generate static files"></a>Generate static files</h3><figure class="highlight bash"><table><tr><td class="gutter"><pre><span class="line">1</span><br></pre></td><td class="code"><pre><span class="line">$ hexo generate</span><br></pre></td></tr></table></figure><p>More info: <a href="https://hexo.io/docs/generating.html">Generating</a></p><h3 id="Deploy-to-remote-sites"><a href="#Deploy-to-remote-sites" class="headerlink" title="Deploy to remote sites"></a>Deploy to remote sites</h3><figure class="highlight bash"><table><tr><td class="gutter"><pre><span class="line">1</span><br></pre></td><td class="code"><pre><span class="line">$ hexo deploy</span><br></pre></td></tr></table></figure><p>More info: <a href="https://hexo.io/docs/one-command-deployment.html">Deployment</a></p>]]></content>
    
    
      
      
    <summary type="html">&lt;p&gt;Welcome to &lt;a href=&quot;https://hexo.io/&quot;&gt;Hexo&lt;/a&gt;! This is your very first post. Check &lt;a href=&quot;https://hexo.io/docs/&quot;&gt;documentation&lt;/a&gt; for</summary>
      
    
    
    
    
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title>Blockchain and Logistics</title>
    <link href="https://wyt.icu/2024/08/07/Blockchain-and-Logistics/"/>
    <id>https://wyt.icu/2024/08/07/Blockchain-and-Logistics/</id>
    <published>2024-08-06T21:44:11.000Z</published>
    <updated>2024-08-06T14:48:10.000Z</updated>
    
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Blockchain, like the logistics supply chain, exists as a chain. But since the creation of blockchain, it has not been taken seriously, and the reasons for this are all attributed to the fact that it is too slow to be accepted by the majority of enterprises because it is too slow to be processed and too costly to be deployed. Today’s blockchain industry is on the verge of becoming a sunset industry.</p><p>Unlike the blockchain, the supply chain is an important part of the logistics system, which is a network of facilities and distribution options that form a team of suppliers and buyers to fulfill the function of purchasing raw materials, making intermediate and final products, and then delivering the final product to the user in the form of a relay race team. Simply put, a supply chain is not just like renting a storefront and opening a supermarket, but a chain that ties products together from production to distribution.</p><p><em>The following quote is from Wikipedia</em></p><blockquote><p>A <strong><a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Supply_chain">supply chain</a></strong>, sometimes expressed as a “supply-chain”,[<a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Supply_chain#cite_note-1">1]</a> is a complex <a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Logistics">logistics</a> system that consists of facilities that convert raw materials into <a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Finished_product">finished products</a> and distribute them[<a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Supply_chain#cite_note-2">2]</a> to end consumers[<a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Supply_chain#cite_note-Ghiani_2004-3">3]</a> or end <a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Customer">customers</a>.[<a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Supply_chain#cite_note-harrison-godsell-4">4]</a> Meanwhile, <a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Supply_chain_management">supply chain management</a> deals with the flow of goods within the supply chain in the most efficient manner.[<a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Supply_chain#cite_note-5">5]</a></p></blockquote><blockquote><p>In sophisticated supply chain <a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/System">systems</a>, used products may re-enter the supply chain at any point where <a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Residual_value">residual value</a> is recyclable. Supply chains link <a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Value_chain">value chains</a>.[<a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Supply_chain#cite_note-6">6]</a> Suppliers in a supply chain are often ranked by “tier”, with first-tier suppliers supplying directly to the client, second-tier suppliers supplying to the first tier, and so on.[<a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Supply_chain#cite_note-7">7]</a></p></blockquote><blockquote><p>The phrase “supply chain” may have been first published in a 1905 article in <em><a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/The_Independent_(New_York_City)">The Independent</a></em> which briefly mentions the difficulty of “keeping a supply chain with India unbroken” during the <a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/British_expedition_to_Tibet">British expedition to Tibet</a>.[<a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Supply_chain#cite_note-8">8]</a></p></blockquote><p><strong>But what’s the connection between supply chain and blockchain?</strong></p><p>There are many similarities between the two, such as both being composed in the form of a chain. The manufacturing supply chain consists of supply, manufacturing, and distribution, whereas blockchain consists of one block at a time.</p><p>They are also different in many ways, and as stated at the beginning of the article, blockchain is not well regarded, whereas supply chain is relevant to our lives. From online shopping to after-sales goods have the figure of the supply chain, as for the blockchain, we hear the most is Bitcoin. Even though the Bitcoin ETF is now approved, it’s still a high-risk investment</p><p><em>Are you confused: why is the title blockchain and logistics when the author keeps talking about supply chain and blockchain.</em></p><p>In fact, logistics also encompasses the supply chain. Logistics is a big scope that contains a lot of things, but the most common logistics we see is courier, so much so that many people think that all logistics students graduate to be a courier.</p><p>The supply chain is actually only a very small part of logistics, but it is the most essential part of logistics.</p><p><strong>How should the logistics supply chain be integrated with blockchain?</strong></p><p>That’s the theme of the day.</p><p>The biggest problem facing the logistics system nowadays is the problem of personal privacy leakage. Enterprises can easily see all the user’s information in the background. So an encrypted logistics platform should be promoted and constructed. But we can’t pin our hopes on people; after all, people are subjective and don’t always run in compliance with a well-written code like a machine. </p><p>Applying smart contracts to logistics systems to automate orders. As an example, the background of a logistics company will not display the user’s personal information, if user A buys a toy, his purchase information will be in encrypted form on the blockchain, and no one can change it.</p><p>I envision a logistics blockchain system where user A registers on our platform to generate a set of private keys locally and public keys on the server. When he receives the goods he needs to sign on his phone to prove that the goods are his. </p><blockquote><p>Hash: dc0613dae17b4354484b7a7cd50e28a8f37b4c5e<br>Status: Delivering<br>Block: 187283<br>Timestamp: Nov-28-2023 12:27:23 PM +UTC<br>From: HJSW08 (Company: ABC Logistics)<br>To: GIWAU900 (User: John Doe)<br>Items (Encrypted): b61e11d20c784c7f8784b3e9088a41550d0d252f<Plush Toy><br>Item Value: $200<br>Transaction Fee: $20</p></blockquote><p>The above is just an example of one kind of blockchain explore.</p><p><strong>Below we explore the realisability of this logistics blockchain</strong></p><p>Fully homomorphic encryption is a new encryption technique that allows various computations such as addition, multiplication, etc. to be performed on encrypted data without decrypting the data. In this way, the data remains encrypted throughout the processing.</p><p>In addition, combining full homomorphic encryption (FHE) with logistics systems can significantly improve the privacy protection of logistics data and ensure the security of sensitive information during data processing and transmission. Here are some specific application scenarios and advantages:</p><p><strong>Supply Chain Management</strong></p><ul><li>Secure data sharing: Logistics supply chain involves multiple participants such as suppliers, manufacturers, transport companies and retailers, FHE ensures that all sensitive information remains encrypted when data is shared among these participants and can only be decrypted and viewed by authorised parties.</li><li>Encrypted inventory management: Individual warehouses and logistics centres can use FHE to process and analyse encrypted inventory data for optimal inventory management without disclosing specific inventory information.</li></ul><p><strong>Transport Process Monitoring</strong></p><ul><li>Encrypted real-time tracking: Real-time data (e.g. location, temperature, humidity, etc.) during the transport process can be encrypted, processed and transmitted using FHE to ensure that the data is not stolen or tampered with during transmission.</li><li>Encrypted Route Optimisation: Transport companies can use FHE to perform route optimisation calculations on encrypted transport data to ensure that the best transport routes are chosen, while protecting the privacy of transport data.</li></ul><p><strong>Customer Data Protection</strong></p><ul><li>Encrypted customer information: Customers’ personal information and order details can be encrypted by FHE to ensure privacy protection at all stages of the logistics process.</li><li>Secure data analysis: Logistics companies can analyse customer data in an encrypted state to extract valuable business insights without having to decrypt the data, protecting customer privacy.</li></ul><p><strong>Payment and Financial Management</strong></p><ul><li>Encrypted Transaction Data: With FHE, payment and financial data in logistics systems can be processed and verified in an encrypted state, ensuring the security and privacy of transactions.</li><li>Automated Settlement: Using smart contracts and FHE, logistics companies can automate settlement, improving efficiency while ensuring data privacy.</li></ul><p>FHE can effectively ensure the integrity of user data, and can reduce fraud due to data tampering or leakage, and improve the security of the system, but its shortcomings are also obvious, FHE computational complexity is high, relies on arithmetic power, and has a high cost.</p><p>In short, deploying a logistics blockchain system can effectively improve logistics efficiency, reduce losses due to regulation, and enable global logistics companies to join together to improve the activity of the entire logistics industry.</p>]]></content>
    
    
      
      
    <summary type="html">&lt;p&gt;Blockchain, like the logistics supply chain, exists as a chain. But since the creation of blockchain, it has not been taken seriously, an</summary>
      
    
    
    
    <category term="Web3" scheme="https://wyt.icu/categories/Web3/"/>
    
    
    <category term="web3" scheme="https://wyt.icu/tags/web3/"/>
    
    <category term="blockchain" scheme="https://wyt.icu/tags/blockchain/"/>
    
    <category term="Logistics" scheme="https://wyt.icu/tags/Logistics/"/>
    
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title>What is E-ID2.0</title>
    <link href="https://wyt.icu/2024/08/05/What-is-Eid2/"/>
    <id>https://wyt.icu/2024/08/05/What-is-Eid2/</id>
    <published>2024-08-04T16:02:00.000Z</published>
    <updated>2024-08-04T09:01:02.000Z</updated>
    
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<h1 id="What-is-E-ID"><a href="#What-is-E-ID" class="headerlink" title="What is E-ID?"></a>What is E-ID?</h1><p>E-ID is similar to E-CNY. It is an electronic ID card issued by the state, except that the application scenarios are now very limited. And there are very few platforms that E-ID can be tied to these days. Alipay, for example, Users can bind E-ID on top of Alipay. Nonetheless, it is not accepted by mainstream apps, like WeChat, Jitterbug are not willing to accept it, so much so that it is in a very awkward situation. However, it is undeniable that it does achieve a certain degree of convenience. For example, when I stayed at a hotel, there were still some hotels that recognized E-ID. </p><p>So we can learn that E-ID has both benefits and drawbacks.</p><ul><li><p>Advantages: convenient and fast</p></li><li><p>disadvantages: Transmission in clear text, not secure. Limited usage scenarios</p></li></ul><p>In general, E-ID is a new product in the electronic information age, but still faces many problems.</p><h1 id="National-Network-Identity（NID"><a href="#National-Network-Identity（NID" class="headerlink" title="National Network Identity（NID)"></a>National Network Identity（NID)</h1><p>NID may become a replacement for E-ID, i.e. E-ID 2.0. It uses a new method to prevent leakage of information about a user’s E-ID (though I don’t think that’s feasible).  NID generates a kind of netID for registered users that looks like a blockchain public address. Simply put, the ID number is converted into a string of virtual IDs(NET. Nub.)</p><p>At this stage, however, NID is only in gray-scale testing and not in public beta, the apps it supports are still very limited. </p><p>A number of people have also appeared on the Internet to boycott it because, although it adopts the means of voluntary registration, we cannot rule out the possibility that it will force everyone to register in the future. However, it does defend against the breeding of some false information, such as fraudulent information, rumor mongering, and so on. Unruly elements will gradually diminish because of the NID bind. </p><p>Here are some of the comments from the internet:</p><blockquote><p>Did telecom fraud become less frequent after the real-name telephone system?</p></blockquote><blockquote><p>Apply for a dog license to facilitate management In the future, the length of your tongue and the extent of your tail wagging will be regulated accordingly!</p></blockquote><blockquote><p>This really concerns each and every one of us, the end result of this behavior must be no safety for everyone, don’t make the same mistake with the health code.</p></blockquote><blockquote><p>Hundreds of millions of people’s information is being taken and sold </p></blockquote><p>I’ve only excerpted some of the comments and can’t be comprehensive, but as you can see, the majority of people hold an opposing view of NIDs.</p><p>There are good reviews, though, and here are some of them:</p><blockquote><p>The body is not afraid of the shadow slant, I am voluntary anyway, the future account can also be unified management, change the cell phone number of the account is also convenient, I do not think there is any problem</p></blockquote><blockquote><p>This is the equivalent of an encrypted ID, you only need to provide the app with an encrypted ID, called a network number, which is actually good for privacy, and it’s useless for someone else to open a box and open an encrypted ID, and you don’t have to provide the ID to the app’s company, and the company won’t store your identity data, and data leakage won’t be as bad, and it’s still to be seen how effective it is, but it’s only silly to be a fan of what people say, and what people say.</p></blockquote><blockquote><p>I’m in favor of it. Now that there are so many spies, if you want to use Chinese apps, you have to sign up for this one, and no one will be spared.</p></blockquote><blockquote><p>Should come out earlier, otherwise a bunch of people indiscriminate net violence others, publish rumors, this is like a camera, there is a camera you still dare to petty theft?</p></blockquote><p>I don’t know what you all think of this. I’m neutral.</p><p>Here is a widely circulated image</p><p><img src="https://pic.imgdb.cn/item/66af3f54d9c307b7e969538d.jpg" alt="alt NID"></p><p>Overall, the advantages of NIDs are that they provide better protection against the proliferation of fraudulent information and also protect the privacy of citizens. For example, user A can check in the NID to see which applications his ID card is registered for. However, the disadvantage is also very obvious, if the hacker hacks into the background of NID, it will surely get hold of all the citizens’ information. In short, the network is a double-edged sword, NID can never replace the physical ID card, it can only be used as an auxiliary tool to help people solve some urgent problems, but not as a legal document.</p>]]></content>
    
    
      
      
    <summary type="html">&lt;h1 id=&quot;What-is-E-ID&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;#What-is-E-ID&quot; class=&quot;headerlink&quot; title=&quot;What is E-ID?&quot;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;What is E-ID?&lt;/h1&gt;&lt;p&gt;E-ID is similar to E-CNY. It</summary>
      
    
    
    
    <category term="Essay" scheme="https://wyt.icu/categories/Essay/"/>
    
    
    <category term="Essay" scheme="https://wyt.icu/tags/Essay/"/>
    
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title>The Internet Era: Where is Knowledge Copyright Heading</title>
    <link href="https://wyt.icu/2024/04/14/The-Internet-Era-Where-is-Knowledge-Copyright-Heading/"/>
    <id>https://wyt.icu/2024/04/14/The-Internet-Era-Where-is-Knowledge-Copyright-Heading/</id>
    <published>2024-04-14T14:01:48.000Z</published>
    <updated>2024-04-14T06:02:36.000Z</updated>
    
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<h1 id="Preface"><a href="#Preface" class="headerlink" title="Preface"></a>Preface</h1><p>With the rapid development and widespread adoption of the Internet, the ways in which knowledge, information, and content are disseminated are undergoing profound changes. This transformation not only poses new challenges and issues for knowledge copyright but also provides unprecedented opportunities for the dissemination and sharing of knowledge. Against this backdrop, the rise of artificial intelligence has become a focal point of attention for creators and intellectual property rights holders. However, while artificial intelligence has its unique advantages and promising applications, it also presents certain limitations and challenges. This article will begin with an exploration of artificial intelligence, introducing the solutions and applications of the Story Protocol.</p><h2 id="Opportunities-in-the-Age-of-Artificial-Intelligence"><a href="#Opportunities-in-the-Age-of-Artificial-Intelligence" class="headerlink" title="Opportunities in the Age of Artificial Intelligence"></a>Opportunities in the Age of Artificial Intelligence</h2><p><strong>Creative Design with Generative AI</strong></p><p>Generative AI, such as Midjourney, utilizes advanced algorithms and models to generate images and designs that meet user expectations based on provided descriptions. Here are some specific application scenarios:</p><ol><li>Personalized Design and Creative Generation: Generative AI can quickly produce images, illustrations, or designs that meet user expectations based on their descriptions and requirements, significantly improving the efficiency and quality of personalized design.</li><li>Artistic Creation and Innovation: Artists and designers can utilize generative AI for artistic creation, exploring and experimenting with new artistic styles and forms of expression.</li><li>Product Design and Simulation: In the process of product design and development, generative AI can assist designers and engineers in rapidly generating and simulating design proposals and effects, accelerating the product development cycle.</li></ol><p><strong>Document Processing and Creation with Text-based AI</strong></p><p>Text-based AI, such as ChatGPT-4.0, possesses powerful natural language processing capabilities, allowing it to derive, adapt, and summarize content based on user-provided documents, significantly enhancing the efficiency and quality of document processing and creation. Here are some specific application scenarios:</p><ol><li>Document Derivation and Adaptation: Text-based AI can generate new content and versions based on existing documents and materials, providing creators with more inspiration and options.</li><li>Document Summarization and Extraction: When dealing with a large volume of documents and materials, text-based AI can automatically summarize and extract key information and viewpoints, helping users quickly access and understand the content.</li><li>Writing Assistant and Editing Tools: Text-based AI can serve as a writing assistant and editing tool, offering writing suggestions, grammar checks, and content optimization, assisting users in improving writing quality and efficiency.</li></ol><h2 id="Challenges-in-the-Age-of-Artificial-Intelligence"><a href="#Challenges-in-the-Age-of-Artificial-Intelligence" class="headerlink" title="Challenges in the Age of Artificial Intelligence"></a>Challenges in the Age of Artificial Intelligence</h2><p>With the rapid development and widespread adoption of artificial intelligence technology, especially the extensive application of generative AI in the fields of creation and design, intellectual property issues are becoming increasingly prominent. The production capacity of AI is influenced by large models, and there are numerous similar or identical AI models on the market, posing serious challenges to the intellectual property rights of creators.</p><p><strong>Issues of Model Sharing and Misuse</strong></p><p>Model Misuse and Repetitive Use: Due to the existence of numerous identical or similar AI models on the market, models created by creators can easily be misused or reused by others. For example, a work created by creator A on a certain platform is transformed into an NFT and uploaded to OpenSea, then purchased by user B and resold at a higher price on OpenSea. At this point, user C might screenshot and save the NFT and mint it into their own NFT, which seriously infringes upon the intellectual property rights of the creator.</p><p><strong>NFT and Intellectual Property Protection</strong></p><p>Authenticity and Uniqueness of NFTs: While NFT technology can provide unique identity and ownership proof for digital artworks, there still exist issues of NFTs being copied, counterfeited, or misused in practical applications. Ensuring the authenticity and uniqueness of NFTs, as well as effectively protecting the intellectual property rights of creators, is an urgent problem that needs to be addressed.</p><p>All the aforementioned issues are challenges we are currently facing in the Internet era. So, how can we address these problems?</p><p>Blockchain technology may be the best solution to these issues. Due to its characteristics of decentralization, immutability, and transparency, blockchain technology can provide a more secure, transparent, and reliable protection mechanism for intellectual property rights.</p><hr><h1 id="Story-Protocol-could-potentially-become-the-ultimate-weapon-to-solve-this-problem"><a href="#Story-Protocol-could-potentially-become-the-ultimate-weapon-to-solve-this-problem" class="headerlink" title="Story Protocol could potentially become the ultimate weapon to solve this problem"></a>Story Protocol could potentially become the ultimate weapon to solve this problem</h1><p><em>The Programmable IP layer built for the age of AI</em></p><p><strong>What is Programmable IP?</strong></p><ul><li>Register an ERC-721 NFT as an IP Asset</li><li>Each IP Asset is also associated with an ERC-6551 Token Bound Account — IPA (IP Account)</li></ul><p><img src="https://miro.medium.com/v2/resize:fit:828/format:webp/0*XJJmirWdU5VfOAJ2" alt="typical example"></p><p>Is Story Protocol just that? Actually, it’s much more than that.</p><p>It is also divided into three modules:</p><ol><li>License Module: Facilitates easy adaptation of IP</li><li>Royalty Module: Automates capital interest sharing</li><li>Dispute Module: Allows appeals for non-compliant assets</li></ol><p>I believe you have already read my previous <a href="https://medium.com/@dongkeith6/story-protocol%E7%82%B9%E7%87%83%E9%93%BE%E4%B8%8Aip%E6%96%B0%E7%83%AD%E6%BD%AE-5f3b9dd59527">article</a> and have a basic understanding of Story Protocol. I won’t dwell on it further here. In this article, I will delve into its specific use cases.</p><p>I hope to provide some inspiration for developers!</p><hr><p>The following is for reference only. Please stay tuned for specific use cases when the testnet goes live!</p><p>Use Cases<br>One-Stop Service</p><p>Currently, SP only supports registering existing NFTs as IPAs on the development network and does not directly support “one-stop” minting of NFTs and registering IPAs.</p><p>Such one-stop services may be supported in the future.</p><p>Company-Level IP</p><p>Registering a single NFT obviously cannot meet the needs of large clients. Below is a comparison of the registration processes:</p><p>Individual Registering IP</p><ul><li>Contract Address</li><li>Token ID</li></ul><p>Company Registering IP</p><ul><li>Contract Address</li></ul><p>It is clear that individual registration of IP requires providing a Token ID, and individuals generally do not have the time or technical expertise to create separate contracts for their IP. This may expose individual IP to risks. Although individuals may not mind, large companies definitely would.</p><p>Therefore, company-level IP registration becomes a solution to such issues. Companies can easily create their own smart contracts and register them as IPAs, and all NFTs under this contract belong to the company’s IP assets.</p><p>The benefits of this approach are also reflected in the dispute module. Using this model, SP can easily handle IP disputes between large clients, reducing arbitration costs.</p><p>Of course, the above is just my opinion, and we will have to wait for the product to go live for specifics.</p><p>(Chinese Version: <a href="https://mirror.xyz/0x53A0Fc074E31068CFdBD73B756458546274fEa97/a1q15FNbuWnsYbAeDSBUi1a68rZjsugU8zIXwV0EHB8">https://mirror.xyz/0x53A0Fc074E31068CFdBD73B756458546274fEa97/a1q15FNbuWnsYbAeDSBUi1a68rZjsugU8zIXwV0EHB8</a>)</p><hr><h2 id="Useful-Links"><a href="#Useful-Links" class="headerlink" title="Useful Links"></a>Useful Links</h2><p>Official Website: <a href="https://www.storyprotocol.xyz/">https://www.storyprotocol.xyz/</a></p><p>Discord: <a href="https://discord.gg/storyprotocol">https://discord.gg/storyprotocol</a></p><p>Twitter&#x2F;X: <a href="https://x.com/StoryProtocol"><a href="https://x.com/StoryProtocol">https://x.com/StoryProtocol</a></a></p><p>Official Documentation: <a href="https://docs.storyprotocol.xyz/docs/what-is-story-protocol">https://docs.storyprotocol.xyz/docs/what-is-story-protocol</a></p><p>Choricles Commemorative NFT Contract: 0xbf2575341e0882bbf6ca8769f39ee435fad8ee8d</p><p>Claim Link 1: <a href="https://app.manifold.xyz/c/story-protocol-chronicles">https://app.manifold.xyz/c/story-protocol-chronicles</a></p><p>Claim Link 2: <a href="https://app.manifold.xyz/c/story-protocol-chronicles-2">https://app.manifold.xyz/c/story-protocol-chronicles-2</a></p>]]></content>
    
    
      
      
    <summary type="html">&lt;h1 id=&quot;Preface&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;#Preface&quot; class=&quot;headerlink&quot; title=&quot;Preface&quot;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;Preface&lt;/h1&gt;&lt;p&gt;With the rapid development and widespread adoption</summary>
      
    
    
    
    <category term="Web3" scheme="https://wyt.icu/categories/Web3/"/>
    
    
    <category term="web3" scheme="https://wyt.icu/tags/web3/"/>
    
    <category term="blockchain" scheme="https://wyt.icu/tags/blockchain/"/>
    
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title>What is web3.0</title>
    <link href="https://wyt.icu/2023/10/19/What-is-web3-0/"/>
    <id>https://wyt.icu/2023/10/19/What-is-web3-0/</id>
    <published>2023-10-18T22:34:13.000Z</published>
    <updated>2024-04-14T05:47:46.000Z</updated>
    
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<h1 id="Introduction-to-Web3"><a href="#Introduction-to-Web3" class="headerlink" title="Introduction to Web3"></a><strong>Introduction to Web3</strong></h1><h2 id="Early-internet"><a href="#Early-internet" class="headerlink" title="Early internet"></a><strong>Early internet</strong></h2><p>People used to divide internet into web1.0 and web2.0. Now we’re go through web2.0 era.</p><h3 id="Web1-0-read-only-1990-2004"><a href="#Web1-0-read-only-1990-2004" class="headerlink" title="Web1.0: read-only (1990-2004)"></a><strong>Web1.0: read-only (<em>1990-2004</em>)</strong></h3><p>Web 1.0 was predominantly static websites owned by corporations with little to no interaction between users - individuals rarely created content, leading to it being called the read-only web.</p><h3 id="Web-2-0-Reading-and-Writing-2004-present"><a href="#Web-2-0-Reading-and-Writing-2004-present" class="headerlink" title="Web 2.0: Reading and Writing (2004 - present)"></a><strong>Web 2.0: Reading and Writing (<em>2004 - present</em>)</strong></h3><p>The Web 2.0 era began in 2004 with the advent of social media platforms. The web was no longer read-only; it became a read-write web. In addition to providing content to users, Internet companies began to provide platforms to share user-produced content and engage in user interactions. As more and more people went online, a handful of Internet giants began to control the sea of traffic and value on the Web. Web 2.0 also gave rise to advertising-driven profit models. While users can create content, they do not own it or benefit by realizing it.</p><h3 id="Web-3-0-Can-Read-Can-Write-Can-Own"><a href="#Web-3-0-Can-Read-Can-Write-Can-Own" class="headerlink" title="Web 3.0: Can Read - Can Write - Can Own"></a><strong>Web 3.0: Can Read - Can Write - Can Own</strong></h3><p>No longer depend on companies. Who created it who owner.</p><h3 id="What-is-web3-0"><a href="#What-is-web3-0" class="headerlink" title="What is web3.0"></a><em><strong>What is web3.0</strong></em></h3><p>Different ones have different definitions</p><p><a href="https://aws.amazon.com/what-is/web3/?nc1=h_ls">Quoted from AWS</a></p><blockquote><p>Web3 is an umbrella term for technologies such as blockchain that decentralize ownership and control of data on the Internet. Most Internet applications are controlled by centralized entities that determine how end-user data is stored and used.Web3 (also known as Web 3.0, Decentralized Web, or Semantic Web) technologies allow for community-driven projects rather than centralized management structures. In these projects, end-users control the data, determine pricing, contribute directly to the development of the technology, and have a more significant say in the direction of the project. These technologies have mechanisms that automatically regulate how users interact with each other. Therefore, there is no need for a centralized entity to manage these interactions.</p></blockquote><p><a href="https://ethereum.org/zh/web3/">Quoted from Ethereum</a></p><blockquote><p>Web3 has become an all-encompassing term that represents a new and better vision for the Internet. At its core, Web3 is about returning power to users in the form of ownership through blockchain, cryptocurrencies and non-homogenized tokens. A 2020 post on <a href="https://twitter.com/himgajria/status/1266415636789334016">Twitter</a> hit the nail on the head: Web1 was read-only, Web2 read&#x2F;write, and the future Web3 read&#x2F;write&#x2F;own.</p></blockquote><p>web3 is a cutting-edge concept aimed at being able to express oneself freely without regulation. People are free to create their own platform and own it without it being shut down for other reasons. </p><h3 id="Differences-between-web2-and-web3"><a href="#Differences-between-web2-and-web3" class="headerlink" title="Differences between web2 and web3"></a><strong>Differences between web2 and web3</strong></h3><h4 id="Web2-0"><a href="#Web2-0" class="headerlink" title="Web2.0"></a>Web2.0</h4><p>You only have access to the account and not ownership, and the platform can block your account. The income you earn is extracted by the platform, which means that everything you have is dependent on the platform and not something you actually own. For example, you have 10 million followers on TikTok, but those followers don’t belong to you, they belong to the platform. After leaving the platform, your fans will no longer belong to you. But web3 can solve it.</p><h4 id="Web3-0"><a href="#Web3-0" class="headerlink" title="Web3.0"></a>Web3.0</h4><p>Your fans can follow you on the web3 platform and can hold your <u><font color=red>NFT</font></u> (non-fungible tokens), note that <u><font color=red>NFT</font></u>  are not changeable and are stored on the blockchain forever. No one can change it.</p><hr><p>Reference 1: <a href="https://ethereum.org/en/web3/">Ethereum</a><br>Reference 2: <a href="https://aws.amazon.com/what-is/web3/?nc1=h_ls">AWS</a></p>]]></content>
    
    
      
      
    <summary type="html">&lt;h1 id=&quot;Introduction-to-Web3&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;#Introduction-to-Web3&quot; class=&quot;headerlink&quot; title=&quot;Introduction to Web3&quot;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Introduction to We</summary>
      
    
    
    
    <category term="Web3" scheme="https://wyt.icu/categories/Web3/"/>
    
    
    <category term="web3" scheme="https://wyt.icu/tags/web3/"/>
    
    <category term="blockchain" scheme="https://wyt.icu/tags/blockchain/"/>
    
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title>Essay of CET-4 about issue solved</title>
    <link href="https://wyt.icu/2023/09/24/Essay-of-CET-4-about-issue-solved/"/>
    <id>https://wyt.icu/2023/09/24/Essay-of-CET-4-about-issue-solved/</id>
    <published>2023-09-24T14:04:10.000Z</published>
    <updated>2023-10-17T13:06:58.000Z</updated>
    
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<h1 id="First-of-all"><a href="#First-of-all" class="headerlink" title="First of all"></a>First of all</h1><p>As we all konw, CET-4 is a considerably important test for our undergraduates. I’m about to give you some suggestions for CET-4’s essay about issue sloved.</p><h2 id="Introduction"><a href="#Introduction" class="headerlink" title="Introduction"></a>Introduction</h2><p>In the CET-4 test, there are more types of compositions. They are issue sloved, opinion selection, interpretation phenomenon, and some others, but mojar of compositions are 3 types. Okay, let’s start isuue solved.</p><h3 id="Ways"><a href="#Ways" class="headerlink" title="Ways"></a>Ways</h3><h4 id="Reference-from-Chatgpt"><a href="#Reference-from-Chatgpt" class="headerlink" title="Reference from Chatgpt"></a>Reference from Chatgpt</h4><hr><blockquote><p><strong>Dirctions</strong>: For this part, you allowed 30 minutes to write a short essay on the importance of reading ability and how to develop it. You should write at least 120 words but no more than 150 words.</p></blockquote><hr><p>According to this subject. We can get information that it is an issue solved. Therefore, what should we write this composition? Following the some advice in Chatgpt. (It will be too complicated to ctrlor)</p><blockquote><p>Certainly, here are some suggestions to expand and enhance your essay on the importance of reading ability and how to develop it:</p><ol><li><strong>Provide Real-Life Examples</strong>: Include anecdotes or examples of individuals who have benefited significantly from their reading abilities. This could be a famous personality, a historical figure, or even a personal experience if applicable.</li><li><strong>Highlight the Benefits</strong>: Elaborate further on the specific benefits of reading ability. Discuss how it can improve one’s problem-solving skills, empathy, and even mental health. Show how it’s not just about acquiring information but also about personal growth.</li><li><strong>Address Challenges</strong>: Mention common challenges people face in developing reading habits, such as distractions, time constraints, or lack of interest. Offer strategies to overcome these obstacles, like setting aside dedicated reading time or exploring various genres.</li><li><strong>Emphasize Lifelong Learning</strong>: Stress that reading is not limited to formal education but is a skill that continues to be valuable throughout one’s life. Encourage the idea that it’s never too late to start or improve one’s reading ability.</li><li><strong>Discuss Digital Reading</strong>: In today’s digital age, acknowledge the shift towards online content and e-books. Explain how individuals can adapt their reading habits to this digital landscape while still reaping the benefits.</li><li><strong>Promote a Diverse Reading Diet</strong>: Emphasize the importance of reading various types of materials, including fiction, non-fiction, newspapers, and academic articles. This diversity can help individuals become more well-rounded readers.</li><li><strong>Mention Resources</strong>: Suggest resources like libraries, book clubs, and online platforms where individuals can find reading material and engage with like-minded readers.</li><li><strong>Include a Personal Touch</strong>: If you have a personal story related to the topic, share it to make the essay more relatable and engaging.</li><li><strong>Summarize Key Points</strong>: In your conclusion, reiterate the main points of the essay and emphasize the overarching message about the significance of reading ability.</li></ol></blockquote><p>Therefore, it returned a composition.</p><blockquote><p>Title: The Significance of Reading Ability and How to Cultivate It<br>  Reading is an indispensable skill that serves as a cornerstone of lifelong learning and personal development. It is the gateway to acquiring knowledge, expanding vocabulary, and enhancing critical thinking abilities. In today’s information-driven world, the importance of reading ability cannot be overstated.<br>  First and foremost, reading is the primary means of accessing information. Whether it’s for academic research, professional growth, or personal enrichment, the ability to read effectively is essential. Furthermore, strong reading skills empower individuals to communicate more effectively, both in writing and in spoken language. A rich vocabulary and comprehension of various writing styles are invaluable assets in any profession.<br>  To develop and nurture reading ability, one must establish a reading routine. Start by choosing books or materials that align with your interests and gradually challenge yourself with more diverse genres. Reading regularly not only improves fluency but also broadens your horizons. Additionally, actively engaging with the material through highlighting, taking notes, or discussing it with others enhances comprehension and retention.<br>  In conclusion, reading is the key to unlocking a world of knowledge and personal growth. By cultivating a habit of reading and actively engaging with the material, individuals can harness the power of this essential skill and embark on a lifelong journey of learning and self-improvement.</p></blockquote><p>It is difficulty for us to compose this essay like this way. Therefore, I will tell you a simple way to write this.</p><h4 id="Note-of-me"><a href="#Note-of-me" class="headerlink" title="Note of me"></a>Note of me</h4><p>We have just three way to compose it. </p><ul><li>It is an omnipotent stence that with the rapid development of <font color=red><strong>education, society, economy, and etc…</strong></font>, it is of great necessity for <font color=blue><strong>us, people, undergraduates</strong></font> to develop their reading ability. </li><li>When we write this, we can write the following solutions could account for this <font color=green><strong>problem, issue, phenomenon</strong></font>. Actually it just addmits us say superfluous words.</li><li>Then we can write our main point. “First and foremost, there is no doubt that we could <u>read more books on profession</u>. Based on a most recent survey, a majority of successful social elites admit that they prefer reading more English books.</li><li>“Furthermore, it is beneficial for undergraduates to access much knowledge in books.” It is as the second point.</li><li>Of course, it do not enough to clarify our points. So we need to use an omnipotent proverb. <font color=red>“Where ther is a will, there is a way. Where there are books, there is knowledge.”</font></li><li>“Therefore, our reading ability need to improve.” At last, we have written the second point.</li><li>Now we start write the last point. “Last but not least, no one can deny that it is high time that <u>we can access more information in books.”</u></li><li>And next we can highlight this last point that only in this way, can we access more couldn’t get in class. </li><li>In the last paragraph, we can make a conclusion to underline the main point how to develop it. “In the word, it is considerably clear that we should promote our reading ability. If we try our almost to develop our reading ability, the future of our lives will be both proming and rosy.”</li></ul><h1 id="End"><a href="#End" class="headerlink" title="End"></a>End</h1><p>From this way, you can clearly know how to write issue solved. It is very easy.<br>Let’s look at the full composition.</p><hr><blockquote><p>With the rapid development of education, it is of great necessity for undergraduates to develop their reading ability. The following solutions could account for this issue.<br>First and foremost, there is no doubt that we could read more books on the profession. Based on a most recent survey, a majority of successful social elites admit that they prefer reading more English books.<br>Furthermore, it is beneficial for undergraduates to access much knowledge in books. Where there is a will, there is a way. Where there are books, there is knowledge. Therefore, our reading ability needs to improve.<br>Last but not least, no one can deny that it is high time that we can access more information in books. only in this way, can we access more couldn’t get in class.<br>In the word, it is considerably clear that we should promote our reading ability. If we try our almost to develop our reading ability, the future of our lives will be both promising and rosy.</p></blockquote><p>If you have other questions, please email me.<br>email: <a href="mailto:&#x64;&#111;&#x6e;&#103;&#x6b;&#101;&#105;&#116;&#104;&#x36;&#64;&#109;&#x61;&#x69;&#108;&#x2e;&#99;&#x6f;&#x6d;">&#x64;&#111;&#x6e;&#103;&#x6b;&#101;&#105;&#116;&#104;&#x36;&#64;&#109;&#x61;&#x69;&#108;&#x2e;&#99;&#x6f;&#x6d;</a><br>Thanks!!!</p>]]></content>
    
    
      
      
    <summary type="html">&lt;h1 id=&quot;First-of-all&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;#First-of-all&quot; class=&quot;headerlink&quot; title=&quot;First of all&quot;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;First of all&lt;/h1&gt;&lt;p&gt;As we all konw, CET-4 is a con</summary>
      
    
    
    
    <category term="English learning" scheme="https://wyt.icu/categories/English-learning/"/>
    
    
    <category term="CET-4" scheme="https://wyt.icu/tags/CET-4/"/>
    
    <category term="Essay" scheme="https://wyt.icu/tags/Essay/"/>
    
  </entry>
  
</feed>
